securekeyconcierge.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy - SecureKey Concierge

This Privacy Policy explains how SecureKey Technologies Inc. (“ **SecureKey** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **we** ”) collects, uses, discloses, stores, safeguards and retains your Personal Information. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may not use our website, services or products.

### **  
Personal Information**

“ **Personal Information** ” means information, other than business contact information, about an identifiable individual.

You should exercise discretion when disclosing your Personal Information to us, and should not disclose sensitive or confidential information that you wish to remain private.

### **  
Application**

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information that we collect when you use our website or services, and to public Personal Information that we may collect from third party websites.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies or other entities that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. Any Personal Information that you supply, or authorize us to supply to any third parties is governed by the privacy policies of those third parties.

### **  
Collection and Use**

Some examples of the types of information that we may collect include:

(i)      contact information, such as your name, address, telephone number, email address;

(ii)     usage information and history, such as your usernames, internet protocol (IP) addresses, support ticket history, and website usage information;

(iii)    meaningless but unique numbers (MBUN); and

(iv)    persistent anonymous identifiers (PAI).

We will collect and use your Personal Information in connection with the provision of products and services from our website including: (i) delivery of our services, such as our authentication service(s) or our identity service(s), (ii) carrying out transactions that you have requested, (iii) for billing purposes, (iv) in order to communicate with you about new products and services, and promotional offers, (v) to prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities, and (vi) managing recruitment and employment relationships. We may use your Personal Information, in conjunction with information available from third parties, to provide the complete functionality of our services.

We may use various kinds of software devices to collect information about Internet use. Small files called “cookies” may be attached to your web browser. These files identify your browser and save information so that our servers can track web browsers. We use cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer. You can set your browser to disable cookies, but our website may not work properly if you disable cookies.

### **  
Disclosure**

We may share your Personal Information with our corporate affiliates to carry out transactions that you request or to make our business, or that of our corporate affiliates, more responsive to your needs. We will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any Personal Information — including customer names and addresses — without the consent of the customer.

We may share your Personal Information with third parties that we engage to provide products and services on our behalf, or to third parties on whose behalf we collect your Personal Information.  We will also not disclose your Personal Information to third parties for the purposes of the third party marketing products to you.

We may disclose your Personal Information: (a) to any governmental authority as part of an investigation to determine our compliance with any applicable law, rule or regulation (including privacy laws, rules and regulations); (b) in response to a court order, subpoena, discovery request or other lawful judicial or administrative proceeding; (c) in order to comply with an applicable law, rule or regulation; and (d) in good faith, to protect or defend our rights or property, or the rights or property of other customers or users.

### **  
Security**

We have implemented reasonable technology and security features appropriate to the sensitivity of the information, including the use of encryption, to safeguard the privacy of your Personal Information from unauthorized access or improper use.

### **  
Accuracy**

If any of your Personal Information collected or stored by us or our service providers is not accurate, complete or up-to-date, please contact our Chief Privacy Officer so that we can correct the information or direct you to the third party responsible for correcting the information.

### **  
Data Retention**

Your Personal Information will be retained only as long as necessary for the purposes for which it was collected, or until you request that we delete it, in which case it will be deleted in accordance with (and subject to) our data retention policy and our legal obligations.

### **  
Withdrawal of Consent**

You may withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information at any time.  To do this, please contact our Chief Privacy Officer.  Withdrawal of your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information will result in you being unable to continue to use our website or services.

### **  
Privacy Officer**

If you have any concerns about our online Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact our Chief Privacy Officer at [cpo@nullsecurekey.com](mailto:cpo@securekey.com) or by mail at:

Chief Privacy Officer

SecureKey Technologies Inc.

4101 Yonge Street, Suite 501

Toronto, Ontario M2P 1N6

### **  
Changes in Practices**

We may change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time. We will inform you of any changes that we make by indicating that such an update has occurred as a notice on our website, or by another means, such as by e-mailing you a notice of the change.
